{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": {
        "theme": [
          {
            "Question": "Which TV show stars Bryan Cranston as a high school chemistry teacher turned meth manufacturer?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Breaking Bad",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Better Call Saul",
              "The Walking Dead",
              "Dexter"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Breaking Bad aired from 2008 to 2013 and is hailed as one of the greatest television series of all time, earning 16 Primetime Emmy Awards."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In the show 'The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel,' what is Midge Maisel's profession?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Stand-up comedian",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Chef",
              "Lawyer",
              "Doctor"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Midge Maisel, portrayed by Rachel Brosnahan, discovers her knack for comedy after her husband leaves her and becomes a successful stand-up comedian in the 1950s."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which TV show features a group of friends living in New York City and revolves around their personal and professional lives?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Friends",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "How I Met Your Mother",
              "The Big Bang Theory",
              "New Girl"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Friends aired from 1994 to 2004 and remains popular for its iconic characters, memorable catchphrases, and relatable storylines."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the bar in the television series 'Cheers'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Cheers",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "The Hoot Owl",
              "The Regal Beagle",
              "The Drunken Clam"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Cheers' is set in the Cheers bar, where the main characters, including Sam Malone and Diane Chambers, form enduring relationships amidst comedic mishaps."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who plays the lead role in the TV show 'Orange is the New Black'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Taylor Schilling",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Viola Davis",
              "Lena Headey",
              "Emilia Clarke"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Taylor Schilling portrays Piper Chapman, a woman incarcerated in a women's federal prison, in the acclaimed comedy-drama series."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which TV show does a high school teacher start cooking and selling meth after being diagnosed with cancer?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Weeds",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Breaking Bad",
              "Ozark",
              "The Sopranos"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Weeds' stars Mary-Louise Parker as a suburban widow who turns to selling marijuana to support her family. The show blends comedy and drama."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which TV show follows the lives of a group of high school students in a fictional town called Capeside?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Dawson's Creek",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Beverly Hills, 90210",
              "The O.C.",
              "One Tree Hill"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Dawson's Creek, known for its coming-of-age storytelling, features characters navigating friendship, love, and dreams as they transition into adulthood."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who plays the lead role in the TV show 'Scrubs'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Zach Braff",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Matthew Perry",
              "Neil Patrick Harris",
              "Alec Baldwin"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Zach Braff portrays John 'J.D.' Dorian, a young doctor navigating the challenges of medical residency while forming lasting bonds with colleagues and patients."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which TV show does a chemistry teacher turn to producing and selling meth with a former student?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Breaking Bad",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "The Sopranos",
              "Mad Men",
              "The Wire"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Breaking Bad's Walter White, portrayed by Bryan Cranston, descends into the criminal underworld alongside former student Jesse Pinkman, brilliantly portrayed by Aaron Paul."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which TV show centers around a woman who starts to work as a bartender after her husband files for divorce?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Cougar Town",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Parks and Recreation",
              "30 Rock",
              "New Girl"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Courteney Cox stars as Jules Cobb in 'Cougar Town,' a comedy-drama series that humorously explores the complexities of relationships and adult friendships."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which TV show does a woman navigate the challenges of being a single mother while pursuing a career in stand-up comedy?",
            "TrueAnswer": "The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Gilmore Girls",
              "Fleabag",
              "Veep"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Rachel Brosnahan's character, Midge Maisel, breaks free from societal norms to pursue her passion for comedy in an era when it was uncommon for women to perform stand-up."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who plays the lead in the TV show 'Glee' as the passionate high school Spanish teacher?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Matthew Morrison",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Lea Michele",
              "Cory Monteith",
              "Jane Lynch"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Matthew Morrison takes on the role of Will Schuester, who revives the school's glee club and fosters the talents of the students in 'Glee.'"
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which TV show does a mother manipulate her son to rise to power in the drug cartel she leads?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Animal Kingdom",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Sons of Anarchy",
              "Ozark",
              "Queen of the South"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Animal Kingdom' intricately weaves family dynamics and criminal activity, with Smurf Cody, portrayed by Ellen Barkin, at the helm of the criminal organization."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which TV show revolves around a choir director who aims to win national competitions with his choir group?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Glee",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Smash",
              "Crazy Ex-Girlfriend",
              "Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The vibrant and melodic journey of Will Schuester, played by Matthew Morrison, in 'Glee' captures the exploration and celebration of individuality and talent."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who portrays the cynical and witty tech executive in the TV show 'The IT Crowd'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Richard Ayoade",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Chris O'Dowd",
              "Noel Fielding",
              "Matthew Berry"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Richard Ayoade shines as Maurice Moss, the quirky and knowledgeable member of the IT department, in the British comedy-drama 'The IT Crowd.'"
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which show does a group of friends navigate the complexities of adult life in the city of San Francisco?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Looking",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Girls",
              "Sex and the City",
              "Friends"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Looking' chronicles the lives of three friends, exploring themes of love, friendship, and identity, while navigating the vibrant backdrop of San Francisco."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who is the creator of the television series 'The Mindy Project' and also portrays the lead character?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Mindy Kaling",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Tina Fey",
              "Amy Poehler",
              "Mindy Kaling"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Mindy Kaling brings to life Dr. Mindy Lahiri, an accomplished obstetrician navigating the challenges of love, career, and friendships, in 'The Mindy Project.'"
          },
          {
            "Question": "In which TV show does a former lawyer start a new career as a high school science teacher?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Better Call Saul",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Prison Break",
              "Suits",
              "The Good Wife"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Better Call Saul' serves as a prequel to 'Breaking Bad' and delves into the transformation of Jimmy McGill, portrayed by Bob Odenkirk, into the infamous lawyer Saul Goodman."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who plays Selina Meyer, the Vice President and later President of the United States, in the TV show 'Veep'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Julia Louis-Dreyfus",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Amy Poehler",
              "Tina Fey",
              "Mindy Kaling"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Julia Louis-Dreyfus's portrayal of Selina Meyer in 'Veep' earned her numerous awards, including six consecutive Primetime Emmy Awards for Outstanding Lead Actress in a Comedy Series."
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  ]
}